Guide to the Records of the Public History Program RG 20.9
New York University Archives
- Series IV: Activities, 1981-2002
  - Subseries A: Public History Workshops, 1981-2002
    - New York University Workshop, 1988-89: Student Work M-S, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 11)
      - Nelson, Pamela and Karen Sotiropoulos, "An Uneasy Alliance: NYU and Its Communities Since 1900: Women at NYU from 1890-1930.", May 6, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 11)
      - Nelson, Pamela, "Women and the University in the 1920s: The Early Career of Dorothy McSparran Arnold at New York University.", December 20, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 11)
      - Sotiropoulos, Karen, "Women in Law at NYU, 1890-1920.", Spring 1989 (Box 4, Folder 11)
      - Sporn, Pam, "The Cold War, The Mural and Radicals: A Study of NYU's Post World War II Student Left.", February 6, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Chinatown Workshop, 1989-90: Planning and Publicity, 1989-1990 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Chinatown Workshop, 1989-90: Student Work, 1989-1990 (Box 4, Folder 13)
      - Bell, Stacey, " 'You Say Tomato Paste -- We Say Marinara': The Great Debate Over the School Achievement of the Italian-American Child.", December 21, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 13)
      - Bernstein, Molly, "American Images of China in 1937: A Media Example.", December 19, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 13)
      - Drucker, Ilana, "Theory Versus Reality: A Re-examination of Americanization, the Public School, and the Italian-American Student.", December 19, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 13)
      - Greene, Janet Wells, "Real Estate on Mulberry Street: Draft III.", February 1, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 13)
      - Bernstein, Rachel and Judith Hasbrouck Holzer, "Mulberry Street in Transition.", December 18, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 13)
      - McGarry, Molly, "The Chinatown Laundry Workers: Organization and Politics.", December 21, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 13)
      - Neilsen, Kirsten J., "Absent Women: Chinese Women in Chinatown, New York's "Bachelor Society," 1989-1940.", January 8, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 13)
      - Wong, Annette, "Images of Chinatown: One Hundred Years of Tourism.", December 20, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Chinatown Workshop, 1989-90: Reference Material, 1989-1990 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Union Square Workshop, 1990-91: Planning and Publicity, 1990-1991 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Union Square Workshop, 1990-91: Student Work Be-Br, 1990-1991 (Box 4, Folder 16)
      Binder
      This item is a hardcover binder containing paper that is not located in a folder.
      - Berman, John S., "Onto Union Square! The Rise of the Labor Movement in Progressive Era New York.", January 28, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 16)
      - Brancaccio, Joan Cowen, "May Day in Union Square: A Study of the Use of An Urban Space.", Spring 1991 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Union Square Workshop, 1990-91: Student Work G-R, 1990-1991 (Box 4, Folder 17)
      - Gatti, Eileen, "There Goes the Neighborhood: Public Space and the Rapid Transit Question.", November 1990 (Box 4, Folder 17)
      - Raynor, Gregory K., "Townhouse Architecture, Land-Use and Social Selection in Nineteenth Century Union Square.", January 1991 (Box 4, Folder 17)
      - Raynor, Gregory K., "'Space--Free Glorious Space': Architecture and Land Use in Nineteenth Century Union Square.", May 4, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Lefferts Manor Workshop, 1991-92: Planning and Promotion, 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Lefferts Manor Workshop, 1991-92: Student Work A-D, 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 19)
      - Allison, Timothy W., "Prospect Park and the Ordering of Adjacent Neighborhoods.", December 23, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 19)
      - Dähnhardt, Ulrike, "Suburbia Clad in Rowhouse Architecture: The Origins of Community in Lefferts Manor.", Fall 1991 (Box 4, Folder 19)
      - Dähnhardt, Ulrike, "Making the Middle-Class Home in Lefferts Manor.", May 3, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Lefferts Manor Workshop, 1991-92: Student Work Ne-Ni, 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 20)
      - Newman, Renee, "Dancing to a Hollow Drum: Pinkster in New York.", Spring 1992 (Box 4, Folder 20)
      - Newman, Renee, "Pinkster and Slavery in Dutch New York, 1790-1827.", December 26, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 20)
      - Nichols, Elizabeth, "A Doomed Frontier: The Politics of the Lefferts Homestead.", 1991 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Lefferts Manor Workshop, 1991-92: Student Work P, 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 21)
      - Petito, John H., "Covenants, Control and Community.", December 30, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 21)
      - Petito, John H., "The Uses of Oral History: Case Study of a Covenant.", December 18, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Lefferts Manor Workshop, 1991-92: Student Work S, 1991-1992 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      Barcode: 3-1142-04227304-8
      - Smith-Campbell, Charmaine, "A Middle Class Neighborhood in Brooklyn, 1893 to 1948.", 1991 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      - Smith-Campbell, Charmaine, "Dream House: Lefferts & the Democratization of Suburban Living Space 1898-1958.", December 1991 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      - Smith-Campbell, Charmaine, "Grace Reformed Church and the History of the Lefferts Manor Neighborhood, 1850-1950.", 1992 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      - Smith-Campbell, Charmaine, "Transformations: Church & Community in Lefferts Manor.", May 1992 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Lefferts Manor Workshop, 1991-92: Reference Material (Official Publications), 1991-1992 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Lefferts Manor Workshop, 1991-92: Reference Material (Academic Papers), 1991-1992 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Lefferts Manor Workshop, 1991-92: Reference Material (Published Articles), 1991-1992 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Lefferts Manor Workshop, 1991-92: Reference Material (Unpublished Articles), 1991-1992 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Lefferts Manor Workshop, 1991-92: Reference Material (Field Notes), 1991-1992 (Box 14, Folder 1)
      Barcode: 3-1442-04227579-5
    - Lefferts Manor Workshop, 1991-92: Reference Material (Field Notes), 1991-1992 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Lefferts Manor Workshop, 1991-92: Reference Material (Institutional Documents), 1991-1992 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Lefferts Manor Workshop, 1991-92: Reference Material (External Publications), 1991-1992 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Lefferts Manor Workshop, 1991-92: Lefferts Manor Calendars, 1989 and 1990, 1989-1990 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Lefferts Manor Workshop, 1991-92: Lefferts Manor Bound Sourcebook, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Lefferts Manor Workshop, 1991-92: Lefferts Manor Bound Financial Report, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Henry Street Workshop, 1992-93: Planning and Promotion, 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Henry Street Workshop, 1992-93: Student Work A-Mc, 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 7)
      - Dähnhardt, Ulrike, "Henry Street Settlement and Vladeck Houses Project Analysis.", Fall 1991 (Box 5, Folder 7)
      - McNamara, Jane, "'Her Boys': The Henry Street Settlement Boys' Clubs.", Fall 1992 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Henry Street Workshop, 1992-93: Student Work Me, 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      - Melhus, Ingrid, "The Creation of a Mental Hygiene Clinic: The Henry Street Settlement.", Fall 1992 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      - Melhus, Ingrid, "From Neighbors to Clients? The Henry Street Settlement Mental Hygiene Clinic.", April 27, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Henry Street Workshop, 1992-93: Student Work N-Ra, 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 9)
      - Newman, Renee, "Music Tosses Its High Hat Out the Window and Becomes Social Minded: Henry Street Settlement Music School, 1935-1969.", December 1992 (Box 5, Folder 9)
      - Newman, Renee, "Two Schools Under One Roof: Henry Street Music School and the Problem of Constituency, 1930-1960.", December 16, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 9)
      - Nichols, Elizabeth, "Questions Unanswered: Henry Street Settlement and the Vladeck Houses.", 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 9)
      - Raynor, Gregory K., "Conception of Delinquency and Community in the Social Services: The Origins of Mobilization for Youth at the Henry Street Settlement, 1958-1968.", December 1992 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Henry Street Workshop, 1992-93: Student Work Re-So, 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 10)
      - Reilly, Sean P., "The Leading Voices.", December 22, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 10)
      - Sorensen, Candace M., "Drama For Education at Henry Street Settlement.", December 28, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Henry Street Workshop, 1992-93: Reference Material, 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Henry Street Workshop, 1992-93: Photographs, 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Tenement Museum Workshop, 1994-95: Planning and Promotion, 1994-1995 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Tenement Museum Workshop, 1994-95: Student Work A-D, 1994-1995 (Box 5, Folder 14)
      - Deutsch, David, "World of Ours: The Formation of Today's Jewish Lower East Side.", 1994-1995 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Tenement Museum Workshop, 1994-95: Student Work Fi, 1994-1995 (Box 5, Folder 15)
      - Finkelstein, Lori, "Ethnic Festivals on the Lower East Side.", October 17, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 15)
      - Finkelstein, Lori, "Revelry on the Street: Celebrating Italian Saint's Day and the Chinese New Year on Manhattan's Lower East Side 1900-1940.", January 31, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 15)
      - Finkelstein, Lori, "Street Fairs and Cultural Pluralism: Italian Saint's Days and the Chinese New Year on the Lower East Side, 1900-1950.", December 23, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Tenement Museum Workshop, 1994-95: Student Work K-L, 1994-1995 (Box 5, Folder 16)
      - Kastan, Susan, "Organizing Charity on New York's Lower East Side: The Corlears District, 1887-1913.", August 2, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Tenement Museum Workshop, 1994-95: Student Work Lo, 1994-1995 (Box 5, Folder 17)
      - Long, Stephen, "Organizing Orchard Street: The Wholesale Dry Goods Employees Union, Family Class and Socialization.", December 5, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 17)
      - Long, Stephen, "The Alternate Tour of 97 Orchard Street: The Tenement as the Home of Labor.", April 30, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Tenement Museum Workshop, 1994-95: Student Work Ma-Mi, 1994-1995 (Box 5, Folder 18)
      - Mattson, Rachel, "Dog Catchers, Gangs, and Beat Cops: Policing Social Order and Creating Criminals on the Lower East Side, 1880-1920.", January 24, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 18)
      - Mattson, Rachel, "Policing and Crime on the Lower East Side, 1880-1920: The Creation of a Modern 'Criminal Class'.", October 10, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 18)
      - Mitchell, Molly, "Becoming an American in Easy Installments: Material Culture and Consumerism on New York's Lower East Side, 1900-1940.", January 24, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Tenement Museum Workshop, 1994-95: Student Work Mu, 1994-1995 (Box 5, Folder 19)
      - Murphy, Kevin, "Manhood on Mulberry Bend.", December 22, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Tenement Museum Workshop, 1994-95: Student Work N, 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 1)
      Barcode: 3-1142-04227305-5
      - Noonan, Ellen, "Perpetuating A Neighborhood on Canvas: Art and Artists of the Lower East Side, 1900-1940.", January 24, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Tenement Museum Workshop, 1994-95: Student Work P-R, 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      - Presby, Phil, "The Voice of the 'Puny Anonymities': Radical Politics, Civil Liberties, and the Lower East Side.", October 10, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      - Presby, Phil, "Radical Politics and State Repression on the Lower East Side.", January 24, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      - Razlogova, Elena, "Ethnicity in Documentary Photography: Lewis Hine and Berenice Abbott.", January 23, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      - Razlogova, Elena, "The Realest Thing: A comparison of New York Street Scenes, Lewis Hine to Berenice Abbott (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Tenement Museum Workshop, 1994-95: Student Work S-T, 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 3)
      - Selsdon, Helen, "Sickness and Death on the Lower East Side.", 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 3)
      - Spencer, John, "Building Borders: Cooperative Village and Urban Renewal on New York's Lower East Side, 1930-1960.", January 24, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 3)
      - Tarantino, Gina M., "Appearances and Realities: Italian Immigrant Women on the Lower East Side, 1880-1920." (Box 6, Folder 3)
      - Tarantino, Gina M., "The Dialectics of Cultural and Individual Change in the Lives of Italian Immigrant Women in New York City, 1900-1930.", December 11, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Tenement Museum Workshop, 1994-95: Student Work, V, 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 4)
      - Vander Vloed, Dawn, "Fire and Housing Reform in New York City Tenements.", January 24, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 4)
      - Vander Vloed, Dawn, "Tenant Life and Fire.", December 15, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Tenement Museum Workshop, 1994-95: Manuscript, 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Tenement Museum Workshop, 1994-95: Manuscript, 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Tenement Museum Workshop, 1994-95: Multimedia, 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Tenement Museum Workshop, 1994-95: Reference Material, 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Tenement Museum Workshop, 1994-95: Reference Material, 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Loisaida & El Barrio Workshop, 1995-96: Planning and Promotion, 1995-1996 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Loisaida & El Barrio Workshop, 1995-96: Student Work B-Mc, 1995-1996 (Box 6, Folder 11)
      - Kaufman, David, "To Connect or Not To Connect: Creating Cyber Community in Alphabet City.", February 1997 (Box 6, Folder 11)
      - May, Kathleen, "Madonna Worship in East Harlem.", January 28, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 11)
      - McMurray, Erin Elizabeth, "More Than a Mirror to the Past: The Museums of the City of New York and its Relationship with East Harlem.", 1996 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Loisaida & El Barrio Workshop, 1995-96: Student Work P-Re, 1995-1996 (Box 6, Folder 12)
      - Pletscher, Melissa, "Union Settlement.", December 31, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 12)
      - Renner, Liz, "East Harlem 'Intersections': Community, Ethnicity and Public Space in East Harlem, 1934-1967.", December 10, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Loisaida & El Barrio Workshop, 1995-96: Student Work Ro-T, 1995-1996 (Box 6, Folder 13)
      - Rose, Mariel, "Research Scenario.", 1995-1996 (Box 6, Folder 13)
      - Rose, Mariel, "Parades, Politics, Community and El Barrio: 1956-1996.", 1995-1996 (Box 6, Folder 13)
      - Rose, Mariel, "Parades and El Barrio Hispano: 1956-1996.", Fall 1996 (Box 6, Folder 13)
      - Sevcenko, Liz, "The Making of Loisaida.", December 10, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 13)
      - Snyder, Michelle K., "The Urban Catholic Parish in New York City: A Community in Transition. The Hispanic Influence on Catholicism on the Lower East Side.", December 19, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 13)
      - Tran, Lan, "Through the Eyes of the Camera: Examining Advertising and Marketing in East Harlem through Photography Exhibits.", 1995-1996 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Loisaida & El Barrio Workshop, 1995-96: Reference Material, 1995-1996 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Activism in NYC Workshop, 1998-1999 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Activism in NYC Workshop, 1998-1999: Student Work (Box 6, Folder 16)
      - Inouye, Daniel H., "New York City Japanese Americans 1931-1950.", December 20, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 16)
      - Wadell, K., "Change and the New York Catholic Worker Movement, 1933-1940.", January 1999 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Social Activism in Metropolitan Culture Workshop, 2000-2001: Student Work (Box 6, Folder 17)
      - Young, Miriama, "Negotiating the Needs of Neighborhood Through Change.", December 2000 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Public History Workshop, 2000-2001: Student Work (Box 6, Folder 18)
      - Chu, Jolene, "Comfort and Commiseration: Jews and Jehovah's Witnesses in New York City.", Fall 2000 (Box 6, Folder 18)
      - Lang, Eleanor, untitled essay., December 2000 (Box 6, Folder 18)
      - Ukpabi, O.M., "A Bite of a Nigerian Big Apple.", December 23, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 18)
      - Ukpabi, O.M., "The Party.", December 13, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Public History Workshop, 2002-2003: Student Work N (Box 6, Folder 19)
      - Nolan, Sara, "A Window on the Square: Isabel Bishop and the Women of Union Square, 1930-1939.", Spring 2003 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Public History Workshop, 2002-2003: Student Work S (Box 6, Folder 20)
      - Shapiro, Michael, "Union Square Image Journal.", October 29, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 20)
      - Shapiro, Michael, "Uses of History in Union Square.", March 11, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Hudson Square Workshop, 2006-07, 2006-2007 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Exhibiting Class in Post War New York, 2006-07: Student Work, 2006-2007 (Box 17, Folder 1)
      Barcode: 3-1142-04227585-2
      - Bunting, Tracy, "Workin' Their Way Up: Teacher Professionalism in the 1980s.", January 2, 2007 (Box 17, Folder 1)
      - Grunow, Annie, "Class, Race, and the Women's Liberation Movement in New York City.", December 28, 2006 (Box 17, Folder 1)
      - Hart, Naomi, "Class in Postwar New York: Subway Graffiti Writers in the 1970s and 1980s: Working-Class Neighborhoods, Expressing Class, Class Interaction and Social Mobility.", Fall 2006 (Box 17, Folder 1)
      - Hayes, Christopher, "To Defeat the Enemies of Desegregation is to Defeat the Enemies of the Trade Union Movement.", October 27, 2006 (Box 17, Folder 1)
      - Pachucki, Jenny, "Second Class Citizens: The Struggle Between ALPA and ALSSA-TWU.", December 19, 2006 (Box 17, Folder 1)
      - Tuttle, Lilly, "Building the Middle Class: Abraham Kazan and the United Housing Foundation in the Lower East Side.", December 22, 2006 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Subseries B: Public History Forums
    - Public History Forums, 1984-85, 1984-1985 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Public History Forums, 1985-86, 1985-1986 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Public History Forums, 1986-87, 1986-1987 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Public History Forums, 1987-88, 1987-1988 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Subseries C: Miscellaneous Activities
    - Paterson Museum Trip, 1984, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Abraham Lincoln Brigade Film Project Proposal, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Bard College Conference, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Bellevue Hospital Oral History Project, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Lower East Side Oral History Project, 1991-94, 1991-1994 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Video Workshop, 1995 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Speculative Archive Presentation, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Various Events, 1989-2003 (Box 17, Folder 13)
- Series V: Reference Material
  - Program Records Listing at NYU Archives, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    Contents
    This folder contains an early listing of some Public History records before they were processed.
  - Mattingly Personal Reference Notes (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Public History Reference Material (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Archival Reference Material (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - NYU Reference Material (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - New York City Reference Material (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Miscellaneous Reference Material (Box 17, Folder 20)
- Series VI: Multimedia
  Some contents of this series contain personal information that may violate the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (FERPA).
  - 1978-1988
    - 'Public History in NYC,' by McNamara, Miller, and Reaven, 1978 (Box 7, Object 1)
      Format
      Radio Shack HD90 Audio Cassette
      Related individuals
      The program/documentary on this cassette was produced by McNamara, Miller, and Reaven -- likely Jane McNamara, Melody Miller, and Marci Reaven -- all graduated of the NYU Public History program. It should be noted, however, that the tape is dated 1978, before the program was created.
      Barcode: 3-1142-04227306-3
    - Chelsea Workshop, 1983, slideshow accompaniment, 1982 (Box 7, Object 2)
      TDK D60 Audio Cassette
      Contents description
      The material on this cassette was intended to serve as an accompaniment for Margaret Finck and Melody Miller's slideshow, presented at the 1982 Public History Workshop that focused on the Chelsea neighborhood in NYC.
    - Chelsea Workshop, 1983, Oral History Segment, 1982 (Box 7, Object 3)
      Scotch BX 60 Audio Cassette
    - Chelsea Workshop, 1983, slideshow material, 1982 (Box 7, Object 4)
      Photographic 35mm slides
      These slides are most likely those used for Finck and Miller's slideshow at the Chelsea Workshop in 1982.
    - Martin Guerre Interview Excerpts, 1982 (Box 7, Object 5)
      U-matic: 3/4 in. analog video cassette
    - Anita Gulkin interview, Greenwich House, 12/21/1983, by Arlie Scott (Box 7, Object 6)
      Maxell XL II-S 90 Audio Cassette
      Interview Subject
      At the time of this interview, Anita Gulkin was the Executive Director of Greenwich House, a community aid organization based in Greenwich Village. Previously a specialist in drug abuse programs, Gulkin assumed the position of Executive Director of Greenwich House in 1976. In 1991, her title was changed to President and Chief Executive. She died in 1998 from a heart attack at the age of 59.
    - Anita Gulkin interview, Greenwich House, 12/21/1983, copy (Box 7, Object 7)
      TDK D Audio Cassette
      Interview subject
    - 'Wartime Opportunities and Lessons Learned,' radio show, 10/1985, Bread & Roses Historical Collective (Box 7, Object 8)
      The participants of this radio show, hosted by the Bread and Roses Historical Collective, are: Della Brooks, Jimmy Cohen, Sue Kozel, and Lynn Van Nosdall.
      TDK D90 Audio Cassette
    - East Village Workshop, 1986, Part 1 (Box 7, Object 9)
      VHS Cassette Tape
    - East Village Workshop, 1986, Part 2 (Box 7, Object 10)
    - East Village Workshop, 1986, Part 3 (Box 7, Object 11)
    - East Village Workshop, 1986, Part 1 (dub) (Box 7, Object 12)
    - East Village Workshop, 1986, Part 2 (dub) (Box 7, Object 13)
    - East Village Workshop, 1986, Part 3 (dub) (Box 7, Object 14)
    - East Village Workshop, 1986, slides (Box 7, Object 15)
    - East Village Workshop, 1986, slides (Box 7, Object 16)
    - East Village Workshop, 1986, slides (Box 7, Object 17)
    - East Village Workshop, 1986, slides (Box 7, Object 18)
    - East Village Workshop, 1986, slides (Box 7, Object 19)
    - East Village Workshop, 1986, slides (Box 7, Object 20)
    - East Village Workshop, 1986, slides (Box 7, Object 21)
    - Malvina Kent interview, by Nancy Dallett, 11/12/1986 (Box 7, Object 22)
      TDK SA-X90
      Attached note
      A note attached to the cassette reads: 'played basketball, now volunteer for Sr. Citizens program, Staywell
    - Malvina Kent interview, by Nancy Dallett, 11/12/1986, copy (Box 7, Object 23)
    - Greenwich House Workshop, 1987, Bill Moyers documentary (Box 7, Object 24)
    - Greenwich House Workshop, 1987, Part 1 (Box 7, Object 25)
    - Greenwich House Workshop, 1987, Part 2 (Box 7, Object 26)
    - Greenwich House Workshop, 1987, Part 3 (Box 7, Object 27)
    - Greenwich House Workshop, 1987, Part 4 (Box 7, Object 28)
    - Greenwich House Workshop, 1987, Part 1 (dub) (Box 7, Object 29)
    - Greenwich House Workshop, 1987, Part 2 (dub) (Box 7, Object 30)
    - Greenwich House Workshop, 1987, Part 3 (dub) (Box 7, Object 31)
    - Greenwich House Workshop, 1987, Part 4 (dub) (Box 7, Object 32)
    - Greenwich House Workshop, 1987, Part 5 (dub) (Box 7, Object 33)
    - Anita Gulkin interview, Greenwich House, 1/14/1987 (Box 7, Object 34)
      Related event/material
      Since Anita Gulkin was the Director of Greenwich House at this time, it can be assumed that this interview was conducted for the 1987 Public History Workshop that focused on the history of Greenwich House.
    - Anita Gulkin interview, Greenwich House, 1/14/1987, Copy (Box 7, Object 35)
      It can be assumed that this interview was conducted for the 1987 Public History Workshop, which focused on the history of the Greenwich House settlement. Anita Gulkin was the Director of Greenwich House at the time of this interview.
    - Greenwich House Workshop, 1987, 'Greenwich House Catechism' presentation, 1986-1987 (Box 7, Object 36)
      It can be assumed that this cassette is related to the 1987 Public History Workshop, which focused on the history of the Greenwich House settlement organization.